<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">SC</string>
    <string name="hey_boys_wats_up">HEY BOYS WATS UP</string>
    <string name="hello_string">HELLO@string</string>
    <string name="hi_i_am_uppal_balu">hi i am uppal balu</string>
    <string name="hiiiiiiiiiiii">hiiiiiiiiiiii</string>
    <string name="helloaaaa">helloaaaa</string>
    <string name="tooo">TODO</string>
    <string name="uppalbaluu">uppalbaluu</string>
    <string name="tiktok">tiktok</string>
    <string name="ttt">ttt</string>
    <string name="buttton">Button</string>
    <string name="page2">page2</string>
    <string name="too">TODO</string>
    <string name="sub_conspiracy">SUB CONSPIRACY</string>
    <string name="frozen">Frozen</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="denver">Denver</string>
    <string name="illuminati">Illuminati</string>
    <string name="aliens">Aliens</string>
    <string name="todo" />
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="what_if_we_told_you_the_walt_disney_company_created_the_movie_frozen_to_alter_google_s_search_algorithm_so_that_when_people_looked_up_some_variation_of_quot_disney_frozen_quot_information_about_the_movie_and_not_about_walt_disney_himself_being_cryogenically_frozen_would_come_up_screen_rant_writes_that_cigarettes_used_to_be_cropped_out_of_disney_s_hands_in_an_attempt_to_keep_up_with_the_mouse_house_s_family_friendly_branding_so_while_creating_a_hit_movie_to_mess_with_an_internet_algorithm_sounds_nutty_it_kind_of_also_makes_sense_and_if_it_was_intentional_disney_is_full_of_geniuses">What if we told you The Walt Disney Company created the movie Frozen to alter Google\'s search algorithm so that when people looked up some variation of \"Disney Frozen,\" information about the movie—and not about Walt Disney himself being cryogenically frozen—would come up? Screen Rant writes that cigarettes used to be cropped out of Disney\'s hands in an attempt to keep up with the Mouse House\'s family-friendly branding, so while creating a hit movie to mess with an internet algorithm sounds nutty, it kind of also makes sense. And if it was intentional, Disney is full of geniuses.</string>
    <string name="conspiracy_theorists_posit_that_the_denver_international_airport_dia_is_a_hub_for_the_lizard_people_who_run_the_government_and_much_of_the_world_just_read_our_feature_about_it_some_believe_dia_is_the_home_base_of_the_illuminati_while_others_believe_it_s_actually_a_portal_to_hell_with_blucifer_the_giant_blue_horse_sculpture_which_killed_the_artist_who_made_it_with_demonic_glowing_red_eyes_guarding_the_gateway_there_are_the_weird_murals_on_the_walls_depicting_nazi_imagery_and_a_commemoration_capstone_plaque_that_mentions_the_new_world_airport_commission_an_organization_that_does_not_exist_between_that_the_gargoyles_in_jeppesen_terminal_and_the_interactive_gargoyle_that_welcomed_travelers_to_the_quot_illuminati_headquarters_quot_before_correcting_himself_and_welcoming_the_masses_to_quot_denver_international_airport_quot_dia_is_either_poking_fun_at_all_the_conspiracies_surrounding_the_facility_or_they_re_hiding_in_plain_sight">Conspiracy theorists posit that the Denver International Airport (DIA) is a hub for the lizard people who run the government and much of the world. Just read our feature about it. Some believe DIA is the home base of the Illuminati, while others believe it\'s actually a portal to hell, with Blucifer (the giant blue horse sculpture—which killed the artist who made it—with demonic, glowing red eyes) guarding the gateway. There are the weird murals on the walls depicting Nazi imagery and a commemoration capstone plaque that mentions the New World Airport Commission (an organization that does not exist). Between that, the gargoyles in Jeppesen terminal, and the interactive gargoyle that welcomed travelers to the \"Illuminati Headquarters\" before correcting himself and welcoming the masses to \"Denver International Airport.\" DIA is either poking fun at all the conspiracies surrounding the facility, or they\'re hiding in plain sight.</string>
    <string name="in_a_historical_sense_the_term_quot_illuminati_quot_refers_to_the_bavarian_illuminati_a_secret_society_that_operated_for_only_a_decade_from_1776_to_1785_this_organization_was_founded_by_adam_weishaupt_a_german_law_professor_who_believed_strongly_in_enlightenment_ideals_and_his_lluminatenorden_sought_to_promote_those_ideals_among_elites_weishaupt_wanted_to_educate_illuminati_members_in_reason_philanthropy_and_other_secular_values_so_that_they_could_influence_political_decisions_when_they_came_to_power_quot_it_was_pretty_ambitious_for_six_or_nine_guys_but_they_really_wanted_to_take_over_the_world_quot_says_chris_hodapp_the_co_author_of_conspiracy_theories_and_secret_societies_for_dummies_with_alice_vonkannon_the_illuminati_s_goals_and_reputation_often_exceeded_their_means_hodapp_notes_in_its_early_days_the_group_was_just_a_handful_of_people_and_even_at_its_largest_it_only_consisted_of_somewhere_between_650_and_2_500_members_the_group_grew_to_that_size_by_becoming_a_sort_of_sleeper_cell_within_other_groups_illuminati_members_joined_freemason_lodges_to_recruit_members_for_their_own_competing_secret_society">In a historical sense, the term \"Illuminati\" refers to the Bavarian Illuminati, a secret society that operated for only a decade, from 1776 to 1785. This organization was founded by Adam Weishaupt, a German law professor who believed strongly in Enlightenment ideals, and his lluminatenorden sought to promote those ideals among elites. Weishaupt wanted to educate Illuminati members in reason, philanthropy, and other secular values so that they could influence political decisions when they came to power. \"It was pretty ambitious for six or nine guys, but they really wanted to take over the world,\" says Chris Hodapp, the co-author of Conspiracy Theories and Secret Societies for Dummies with Alice VonKannon. The Illuminati\'s goals — and reputation — often exceeded their means, Hodapp notes. In its early days, the group was just a handful of people. And even at its largest, it only consisted of somewhere between 650 and 2,500 members. The group grew to that size by becoming a sort of sleeper cell within other groups — Illuminati members joined Freemason lodges to recruit members for their own competing secret society.</string>
    <string name="the_series_of_boulders_that_make_up_stonehenge_have_long_puzzled_experts_and_provided_material_ripe_for_conspiracy_theorists_most_pertinent_is_the_question_how_were_the_stones_some_weighing_50_tons_transported_and_arranged_to_where_they_sit_today_without_basic_transportation_technology_such_as_wheels_which_were_invented_more_than_five_centuries_after_stonehenge_is_believed_to_have_been_built_there_is_no_obvious_answer_to_how_the_biggest_stones_were_moved_much_of_what_scientists_do_know_about_the_construction_of_stonehenge_is_from_educated_guesses_and_constantly_evolving_research_the_newest_of_which_suggests_that_in_fact_two_of_the_largest_boulders_that_make_up_stonehenge_have_always_been_more_or_less_where_they_sit_today_alternatively_of_course_scientists_could_shun_the_research_and_read_erich_von_d_niken_s_seminal_book_chariots_of_the_gods_which_makes_the_argument_that_many_ancient_megastructures_such_as_stonehenge_the_egyptian_pyramids_and_the_moai_heads_of_easter_island_were_built_using_know_how_passed_down_from_god_like_aliens_to_mankind_says_the_independent_though_why_the_extraterrestrials_would_pass_on_the_knowledge_of_how_to_build_stonehenge_but_not_the_wheel_is_anyone_s_guess">The series of boulders that make up Stonehenge have long puzzled experts and provided material ripe for conspiracy theorists. Most pertinent is the question: how were the stones - some weighing 50 tons - transported and arranged to where they sit today? Without basic transportation technology, such as wheels (which were invented more than five centuries after Stonehenge is believed to have been built), there is no obvious answer to how the biggest stones were moved. Much of what scientists do know about the construction of Stonehenge is from educated guesses and constantly evolving research, the newest of which suggests that in fact two of the largest boulders that make up Stonehenge have always been “more or less” where they sit today. Alternatively of course, scientists could shun the research and read Erich von Däniken’s seminal book Chariots of the Gods?, “which makes the argument that many ancient megastructures such as Stonehenge, the Egyptian pyramids, and the Moai heads of Easter Island were built using know-how passed down from God-like aliens to mankind”, says The Independent. Though why the extraterrestrials would pass on the knowledge of how to build Stonehenge but not the wheel is anyone’s guess...</string>
    <string name="sai_subramanyam_app_developer">Sai Subramanyam - App Developer</string>
    <string name="sc_is_an_app_where_you_can_read_interesting_and_craziest_conspiracy_theories_the_theories_will_be_updated_for_every_2_weeks_and_even_more_features_would_be_added_like_chatsbots_and_more_thank_you_for_downloading_the_app">SC is an app where you can read interesting and craziest conspiracy theories. The theories will be updated for every 2 weeks and even more features would be added like chatsbots and more.Thank you for downloading the app</string>
    <string name="photos_walt_disney_building_disneyland_1_american_producer_director_and_animator_walt_disney_1901_1966_uses_a_baton_to_point_to_sketches_of_disneyland_1955_photo_by_hulton_archive_getty_images_8_gallery_8_images_his_fascination_with_the_future_fueled_rumors_over_the_years_proponents_of_this_seemingly_absurd_rumor_have_cited_the_secrecy_surrounding_disney_s_death_and_burial_as_evidence_of_its_veracity_they_claim_that_news_of_his_passing_was_intentionally_delayed_in_order_to_give_his_handlers_time_to_place_his_body_in_cryonic_suspension_and_that_both_his_funeral_and_the_actual_location_of_his_burial_plot_have_been_kept_secret_as_a_means_of_further_concealing_the_truth_of_his_interment_disney_s_lifelong_interest_in_the_future_projects_such_as_his_epcot_center_experimental_prototype_community_of_tomorrow_and_the_technical_innovations_for_which_he_was_known_throughout_his_career_would_no_doubt_have_lent_the_rumor_a_certain_air_of_truth_while_a_time_magazine_article_about_the_cryonic_freezing_of_a_73_year_old_psychology_professor_also_lent_its_weight_the_assertions_of_two_separate_biographies_of_disney_leonard_mosely_s_disney_s_world_1986_and_marc_eliot_s_walt_disney_hollywood_s_dark_prince_1993_which_claimed_that_an_obsession_with_death_led_disney_to_an_interest_in_cryonics_surely_did_their_part_to_perpetuate_it_through_the_years_as_well_in_a_1972_biography_about_her_father_disney_s_daughter_diane_wrote_that_she_doubted_he_had_even_heard_of_cryonics_photo_united_artists_photofest_disney_s_daughter_has_denied_that_he_s_cryogenically_frozen_the_exact_origins_of_the_rumor_are_uncertain_but_it_first_appeared_in_print_in_a_1969_ici_paris_article_in_which_a_disney_executive_attributed_it_to_a_group_of_disgruntled_animators_seeking_to_have_a_laugh_at_their_late_taskmaster_employer_s_expense_read_next_video_walt_disney_loveable_characters_by_feb_18_2017_celebrity_meet_mary_austin_the_woman_who_stole_freddie_mercury_s_heart_by_colin_bertram_oct_30_2018_celebrity_it_took_walt_disney_more_than_20_years_to_make_mary_poppins_by_brad_witter_nov_16_2018_disney_s_daughter_diane_wrote_in_a_1972_biography_about_her_famous_father_that_she_doubted_her_father_had_even_heard_of_cryonics_it_has_been_further_discredited_by_those_pointing_to_the_existence_of_signed_legal_documents_that_indicate_disney_was_in_fact_cremated_and_that_his_remains_are_interred_in_a_marked_plot_for_which_his_estate_paid_40_000_at_forest_lawn_the_exact_location_of_which_is_a_matter_of_public_record_further_by_all_accounts_disney_was_known_to_be_a_very_private_man_in_life_making_the_quiet_circumstances_of_his_cremation_and_burial_far_from_suspect_and_the_assertions_in_mosely_s_and_eliot_s_biographies_have_been_widely_rejected_as_unfounded_the_science_behind_cryonics_is_still_developing_yet_despite_the_apparent_lack_of_any_credible_evidence_supporting_a_connection_between_it_and_disney_the_existence_of_cryonics_is_very_much_a_reality_since_1964_when_robert_ettinger_published_a_work_discussing_the_plausibility_of_freezing_human_beings_for_the_purpose_of_bringing_them_back_to_life_a_significant_cryonics_industry_has_developed_in_the_united_states_today_companies_such_as_suspended_animation_inc_cryonics_institute_and_alcor_life_extension_foundation_offer_their_clients_the_opportunity_to_have_their_bodies_placed_in_a_large_metal_tank_in_a_state_of_deep_freeze_known_as_cryostasis_for_the_purpose_of_being_restored_to_life_and_complete_physical_and_mental_health_at_a_theoretical_point_in_the_future_when_medical_science_is_advanced_enough_to_do_so_according_to_reports_there_are_hundreds_of_people_being_kept_in_cryostasis_at_facilities_around_the_country_and_thousands_more_that_have_already_made_arrangements_for_their_own_preservation_following_his_death_in_2004_baseball_legend_ted_williams_became_the_highest_profile_person_to_date_to_be_placed_in_cryostasis_cryonics_is_not_without_its_detractors_however_its_science_has_been_largely_dismissed_as_fantastical_still_it_s_the_futuristic_stuff_of_science_fiction_that_maybe_even_disney_himself_would_have_appreciated_ad_by_david_blatty">PHOTOS: Walt Disney Building Disneyland 1_American producer, director, and animator Walt Disney (1901 - 1966) uses a baton to point to sketches of Disneyland, 1955. (Photo by Hulton Archive:Getty Images) 8 GALLERY 8 IMAGES His fascination with the future fueled rumors Over the years, proponents of this seemingly absurd rumor have cited the secrecy surrounding Disney’s death and burial as evidence of its veracity. They claim that news of his passing was intentionally delayed in order to give his handlers time to place his body in cryonic suspension and that both his funeral and the actual location of his burial plot have been kept secret as a means of further concealing the truth of his interment. Disney’s lifelong interest in the future, projects such as his EPCOT Center (Experimental Prototype Community of Tomorrow) and the technical innovations for which he was known throughout his career would no doubt have lent the rumor a certain air of truth, while a Time magazine article about the cryonic freezing of a 73-year-old psychology professor also lent its weight. The assertions of two separate biographies of Disney — Leonard Mosely’s Disney’s World (1986) and Marc Eliot’s Walt Disney: Hollywood’s Dark Prince (1993) — which claimed that an obsession with death led Disney to an interest in cryonics, surely did their part to perpetuate it through the years as well. In a 1972 biography about her father, Disney\'s daughter Diane wrote that she doubted he had even heard of cryonics. Photo: United Artists/Photofest Disney\'s daughter has denied that he\'s cryogenically frozen The exact origins of the rumor are uncertain, but it first appeared in print in a 1969 Ici Paris article in which a Disney executive attributed it to a group of disgruntled animators seeking to have a laugh at their late taskmaster employer’s expense. READ NEXT VIDEO Walt Disney - Loveable Characters BY FEB 18, 2017 CELEBRITY Meet Mary Austin, the Woman Who Stole Freddie Mercury\'s Heart BY COLIN BERTRAM OCT 30, 2018 CELEBRITY It Took Walt Disney More Than 20 Years to Make \'Mary Poppins\' BY BRAD WITTER NOV 16, 2018 Disney’s daughter, Diane, wrote in a 1972 biography about her famous father that she doubted her father had even heard of cryonics. It has been further discredited by those pointing to the existence of signed legal documents that indicate Disney was in fact cremated and that his remains are interred in a marked plot (for which his estate paid $40,000) at Forest Lawn, the exact location of which is a matter of public record. Further, by all accounts, Disney was known to be a very private man in life, making the quiet circumstances of his cremation and burial far from suspect, and the assertions in Mosely’s and Eliot’s biographies have been widely rejected as unfounded. The science behind cryonics is still developing Yet despite the apparent lack of any credible evidence supporting a connection between it and Disney, the existence of cryonics is very much a reality. Since 1964, when Robert Ettinger published a work discussing the plausibility of freezing human beings for the purpose of bringing them back to life, a significant cryonics industry has developed in the United States. Today, companies such as Suspended Animation Inc., Cryonics Institute and Alcor Life Extension Foundation offer their clients the opportunity to have their bodies placed in a large metal tank in a state of deep freeze known as “cryostasis,” for the purpose of being restored to life and complete physical and mental health at a theoretical point in the future when medical science is advanced enough to do so. According to reports, there are hundreds of people being kept in cryostasis at facilities around the country and thousands more that have already made arrangements for their own preservation. Following his death in 2004, baseball legend Ted Williams became the highest-profile person to date to be placed in cryostasis. Cryonics is not without its detractors, however. Its science has been largely dismissed as fantastical. Still, it’s the futuristic stuff of science fiction that maybe even Disney himself would have appreciated. AD BY DAVID BLATTY</string>
    <string name="the_government_was_stealing_parts_of_dead_bodies_because_they_needed_young_tissue_they_recruited_a_worldwide_network_of_agents_to_find_recently_deceased_babies_and_children_and_then_take_samples_and_even_limbs_each_collected_without_notification_or_permission_of_the_more_than_1_500_grieving_families_the_world_only_woke_up_to_the_the_horrific_scientic_history_of_project_sunshine_half_a_century_later_but_there_are_still_a_lot_of_unexplained_mysteries_out_there">The government was stealing parts of dead bodies. Because they needed young tissue, they recruited a worldwide network of agents to find recently deceased babies and children, and then take samples and even limbs – each collected without notification or permission of the more than 1,500 grieving families. The world only woke up to the the horrific scientic history of Project Sunshine half a century later. But there are still a lot of unexplained mysteries out there.</string>
    <string name="Sunshine">sunshine</string>
</resources>